Scammed in Oost?
- Damn it, really?
Get down. They’ll give you something, then you can start trading in your neighborhood.
Move forward, Chupa Chups.
Don’t invite strangers, okay?
I’m not talking to you, man. I’m talking to him.
Open it.
Abdelhak Taheri, sir.
I want the exact coordinates of your South American contact, Auntie Alvarez.
What are you doing?
I have news: Uncle has some major deals with the Mexicans.
Where’s Duane?
I hope your friend will cooperate…
otherwise, it’ll be the end of the road for him… and things.
You said I’d end up like this, didn’t you?
- Wollah, I didn’t teach you that.
I swear he’s coming.
Tell your uncle to screw off, yeah?
A: TONNANO
MY Uncle HAS POPE. BRING THE ARMY NOW.
Listen, Adil, tomorrow in court
you’re going to get hit hard…
it’s gonna be rough,
Hurry up.
Hurry up! We're leaving.
I've gathered the troops.
How many men do we have? - Four. And they're all armed.
I'm going to take care of their mothers today.
I can't rest until this is done. He's family.
Let Goddamn their mothers’ bloodline.
If they don't die today, they'll die tomorrow. Today is the day everything blows up.
Take it easy. We'll track him down.
Yes, we'll find him.
And bring him back. This is bigger than just you.
It’s also about me, right?
We’re going after him.
Understood?
Palace of Justice
So you're finally here? - Yes.
They put my father in an institution.
Completely buried in dirt.
He really can't come back.
Who will help him? God willing.
- Who should help him? - God willing.
In court.
Please take your seats.
The session begins.
We are gathered here today to decide...
whether the detention of Mr. El Haddaoui will be extended.
Therefore, first, I would like to give the floor to the officer.
Thank you, Madam President. Your Honor.
This is the situation, and I won’t mince words.
The prosecution, in cooperation with the IFN,
and the national criminal investigation department
This is the first translated subtitle.
is "Soy yo. Calma." Literally, "It's me. Calm." But in context, it might be better as "It’s me. Stay calm."
Moving on to
Look here, dad.
I brought someone with me.
He’ll help you.
Peace be upon you, Abdelhak.
Do you remember who I am?
Yeah? How are you?
Within the criminal organization...
extremely popular.
Criminals stick to the belief...
that encryption on these devices can't be cracked...
and freely converse.
That's a misconception.
Thanks to our colleagues' relentless efforts...
at the IFN,
we managed to crack the Icelandic servers we seized.
Because of our success in cracking those Icelandic servers,
the prosecution obtained access to
over six million written messages,
just like the familiar WhatsApp messages everyone knows.
We also know that one of his aliases...
is Mr. El Haddaoui's.
'knock-out' / 'KO'.
When mentioning "knock-out" or "KO", it translates directly as "'knock-out' / 'KO'."
And that’s why I can give a preview here.
Esteemed Mr. President, Members of the Court, we request...
that the defendant remain...
in preventive custody for another ninety days...
to allow time for the fiscal authorities...
Let’s thoroughly examine this material.
Thanks.
Keep quiet in the courtroom.
Be silent!
Silence.
Hello.
Let’s move. Let’s go.
Zakaria, stand up.
Zakaria, rise.
Where in the hell were you?
The entire block is blocked off.
Cops everywhere.
It's all right here.
I swear to God, if I see that son of a bitch...
I'll drill two bullets into his head.
Where the hell is the gun?
Come on in.
Everything’s gone.
Hi. Come here.
Come here.