They double-crossed him in Oost.
- Damn, seriously?
Get down. They'll give you something to get started dealing in your neighborhood.
Come on, Chupa Chups.
Don't bring weird people around here, okay?
I'm not talking to you, pal. I'm talking to him.
Open it.
Abdelhak Taheri.
I want the exact location of your South American contact, Tía Alvarez.
What are you doing?
I have news. The guy has dealings with the Mexicans.
Where's Duane?
I hope your friend cooperates... otherwise it'll be curtains for him too.
You taught me that, jerk.
- Wollah, I didn't teach you anything.
I swear he's coming.
Tell your uncle to go to hell, alright?
A: TONNANO! MY UNCLE HAS POPE. BRING THE ARMY.
Listen Adil, tomorrow in court, you'll receive a crushing blow...
...a tough one to swallow, I'm going to nail you.
Hurry up.
Come on, hurry up, let's go.
I have the army organized.
How many? - Four, and they're armed.
Today I'm going to make them pay for this.
I swear, it won't sit well with me. He's family.
I swear, I won't feel good. He's family.
May God curse their mothers.
If they don't die today, they will die tomorrow.
Today is the day everything explodes in their faces.
Calm down. We'll find your cousin.
Yes, we will find him.
And we're going to bring him back. This isn't just about you. It's about me too.
Also me, right?
Let's go get him.
Got it?
PALACE OF JUSTICE
So, you're finally here? - Yes.
They put my father in an institution... buried deep in filth.
He can't come back from this.
Who will help him? - Inshallah.
- Who should help him?
- Inshallah.
The tribunal is now in session.
Please, take a seat.
Court is convened.
We are here to determine...
whether Mr. El Haddaoui's pre-trial detention should be extended.
To begin, I would like to give the floor to the officer.
Thank you, Madam President. Members of the Court.
Straight to the point then.
The prosecution, in collaboration with the IFN, and the national department of criminal investigation...
have made a remarkable discovery.
has led to a spectacular breakthrough.
It's me. Calm down. Look here, Dad.
I brought someone with me. He's going to help you.
Peace be upon you, Abdelhak.
Do you recognize me?
Yes? How are you?
Within the criminal organization...
it is common practice to use so-called PGP phones – extremely prevalent.
it is customary use of so-called PGP phones, extremely popular.
Criminals operate under the assumption...
...that encryption on these devices is unbreakable...
...and allows them to speak freely.
That's a dangerous misconception.
Thanks to the tireless work of our IFN colleagues, we've managed to crack the seized Icelandic servers.
Cracking those Icelandic servers has enabled the prosecution to obtain...
over 6 million written messages—similar to WhatsApp conversations we all recognize.
We also know that one alias used by Mr. El Haddaoui is “knock-out”—or KO for short.
And that's why I can present a preview now.
Esteemed President, members of the Court, we request...
...that the defendant remain in pre-trial detention for an additional 90 days to allow the prosecution...
We also know that one of the aliases...
of Mr. El Haddaoui
is “knock-out”.
Or KO.
And that's why I can do a preview here.
Esteemed President, members of the Court, we request...
that the defendant remain...
in pre-trial detention for another 90 days
to allow the prosecution...
I need to thoroughly analyze that evidence.
Thank you, sir.
Order in the courtroom.
Silence, please.
Quiet!
Hello there.
Come on, come on.
Zakaria, get up here.
Zakaria, you need to come up.
Where the hell have you been?
The whole damn street is blocked off. Cops everywhere.
It's all there.
I swear, if I see that damn bum...
I'll blow his brains out with two bullets.
Where's that gun?
Ibo, please.
Everything vanished.
Hey, come here. Come closer.
Here, come here.
Come here.